girlsintube.com 2014-06-20

# Privacy Policy · Girls in tube - girls in sex, free girls porn videos, porno redtube

This document details important information regarding the use and disclosure of User Data collected on GirlsInTube.com.

The security of your Data is very important to GirlsInTube.com and as such we take all appropriate steps to limit the risk that it may be lost, damaged or misused.

This site expressly and strictly limits its membership and/or viewing privileges to adults 21 years of age and over and having attained the age or viewing pornography rights of majority in their community. All persons who do not meet its criteria are strictly forbidden from accessing or viewing the contents of this Site. We do not knowingly seek or collect any personal information or data from persons who have not attained the age of majority.

 **DATA COLLECTING**

Personal Information: Non-Registered users can watch videos without registering and without any information being processed. However the visitor's IP address and date of birth will be recorded in the event that there is any misappropriation of information and/or content and accessing a number of other features. Posting comments on GirlsInTube.com website the following personal information is requested: username (required), and email address (required) and individual post. All this data with the exception of the email address and IP address becomes publicly accessible information.

Content Uploaded to the site: Any personal information and data content that you voluntarily disclose online becomes publicly available and can be collected and used by others.

Cookies:  When you visit GirlsInTube.com, we may send one or more cookies to your computer that uniquely identifies your browser session. GirlsInTube.com uses both session cookies and persistent cookies. If you remove your persistent cookie, some of the site's features may not function properly.

Log File Information:  When you visit GirlsInTube.com, our servers automatically record certain information that your web browser sends such as your web request, IP address, browser type, browser language, referring URL, platform type, domain names and the date and time of your request. When you visit GirlsInTube.com, our servers automatically record certain information that your web browser sends such as your web request, IP address, browser type, browser language, referring URL, platform type, domain names and the date and time of your request.

Email:  If you contact us or post comments, we may keep a record of that correspondence.

 **USES**

Your Personally identifiable information submitted to GirlsInTube.com is used to provide to the user the website's features and/or special personalized features. Your chosen username (not your email address) is displayed to other Users alongside the content you upload, including comments you send through the GirlsInTube.com etc. We may use your email address without further consent for marketing or administrative purposes (such as notifying you of key website changes or for customer service purposes). We analyze aggregated user traffic information to help streamline our marketing and hosting operations and to improve the quality of the GirlsInTube.com user-experience.

 **DISCLOSURE OF INFORMATION**

If under duty to do so GirlsInTube.com may release data to comply with any legal obligation, or in order to enforce our Terms Of Service and other agreements; or to protect the rights, property or safety of GirlsInTube.com or our subscribers or others. This includes exchanging information with other companies and organizations including the police and governmental authorities for the purposes of protection against fraud or any other kind of illegal activity whether or not identified in the Terms Of Service. It is GirlsInTube.com's policy, whenever possible and legally permissible, to promptly notify you upon an obligation to supply data to any third party. Should you deliberately upload any illegal material GirlsInTube.com shall forward all available information to all relevant authorities and this without notice.

 **SECURITY**

Unfortunately, the transmission of information via the Internet is not completely secure. GirlsInTube.com uses commercially reasonable physical, managerial and technical safeguards to preserve the integrity and security of your personal information. We cannot, however, ensure or warrant the security of any information you transmit to GirlsInTube.com and you do so at your own risk.

 **YOUR RIGHTS**

You are entitled to access and correct your Data by requesting us to do so via the Contact section. If you have additional questions, copyright/abuse reports, suggestions, advertising or business relation proposals then please contact us by using following link.
